{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Bathroom Remodelers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40129/":{"taskOID":40129,"originalTaskOID":40129,"setID":440,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7240,"questionDisplayText":"Extensiveness of Remodel","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How extensively do you want to remodel your bathroom?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11410,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"I plan to maintain existing bathroom floorplan","answerDisplayText":"I plan to maintain existing bathroom floorplan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11411,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"I am considering changes to bathroom floorplan","answerDisplayText":"I am considering changes to bathroom floorplan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7234,"questionDisplayText":"Shower / Bath","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Shower / Bath","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11414,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I want to move or install a new shower or bath","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I want to move or install a new shower or bath","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11415,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I will keep the existing shower or bath as is","answerDisplayText":"No - I will keep the existing shower or bath as is","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7235,"questionDisplayText":"Toilet","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Toilet","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11416,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I will be replacing or moving the toilet","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I will be replacing or moving the toilet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11417,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I will keep the existing toilet as is","answerDisplayText":"No - I will keep the existing toilet as is","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7236,"questionDisplayText":"Cabinets / Vanity","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Cabinets / Vanity","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11418,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the cabinets / vanity","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the cabinets / vanity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11419,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the cabinets / vanity","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the cabinets / vanity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7237,"questionDisplayText":"Countertops","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Countertops","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11420,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the countertops","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the countertops","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11421,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the countertops","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the countertops","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7238,"questionDisplayText":"Sinks","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Sinks","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11422,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the sinks","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the sinks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11423,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the sinks","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the sinks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7239,"questionDisplayText":"Flooring","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Flooring","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11424,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the flooring","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11425,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the flooring","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":160804,"questionDisplayText":"Requires Work on Historical Structure","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Does this project require work on a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":160807,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":160805,"questionDisplayText":"Request for Commercial Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request for a commercial (non-residential) location?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503473,"questionDisplayText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":9,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","shortQuestionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7240,"questionDisplayText":"Extensiveness of Remodel","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How extensively do you want to remodel your bathroom?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11410,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"I plan to maintain existing bathroom floorplan","answerDisplayText":"I plan to maintain existing bathroom floorplan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11411,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"I am considering changes to bathroom floorplan","answerDisplayText":"I am considering changes to bathroom floorplan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11410,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"I plan to maintain existing bathroom floorplan","answerDisplayText":"I plan to maintain existing bathroom floorplan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11411,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"I am considering changes to bathroom floorplan","answerDisplayText":"I am considering changes to bathroom floorplan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7234,"questionDisplayText":"Shower / Bath","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Shower / Bath","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11414,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I want to move or install a new shower or bath","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I want to move or install a new shower or bath","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11415,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I will keep the existing shower or bath as is","answerDisplayText":"No - I will keep the existing shower or bath as is","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11414,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I want to move or install a new shower or bath","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I want to move or install a new shower or bath","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11415,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I will keep the existing shower or bath as is","answerDisplayText":"No - I will keep the existing shower or bath as is","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7235,"questionDisplayText":"Toilet","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Toilet","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11416,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I will be replacing or moving the toilet","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I will be replacing or moving the toilet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11417,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I will keep the existing toilet as is","answerDisplayText":"No - I will keep the existing toilet as is","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11416,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I will be replacing or moving the toilet","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I will be replacing or moving the toilet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11417,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I will keep the existing toilet as is","answerDisplayText":"No - I will keep the existing toilet as is","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7236,"questionDisplayText":"Cabinets / Vanity","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Cabinets / Vanity","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11418,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the cabinets / vanity","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the cabinets / vanity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11419,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the cabinets / vanity","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the cabinets / vanity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11418,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the cabinets / vanity","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the cabinets / vanity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11419,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the cabinets / vanity","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the cabinets / vanity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7237,"questionDisplayText":"Countertops","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Countertops","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11420,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the countertops","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the countertops","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11421,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the countertops","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the countertops","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11420,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the countertops","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the countertops","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11421,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the countertops","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the countertops","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7238,"questionDisplayText":"Sinks","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Sinks","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11422,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the sinks","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the sinks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11423,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the sinks","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the sinks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11422,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the sinks","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the sinks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11423,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the sinks","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the sinks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7239,"questionDisplayText":"Flooring","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Flooring","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7232,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11424,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the flooring","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11425,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the flooring","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11424,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the flooring","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11425,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the flooring","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":160804,"questionDisplayText":"Requires Work on Historical Structure","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Does this project require work on a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":160807,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":160805,"questionDisplayText":"Request for Commercial Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request for a commercial (non-residential) location?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503473,"questionDisplayText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":9,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","shortQuestionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40129/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40129,"taskName":"Bathroom - Remodel","taskDescription":"Remodel a Bathroom","xmTaskDescriptor":"Bathroom Remodelers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":24,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"addition major makeover finishing finish","textMessagingName":"Remodel Bathrm","rolloverLongDesc":"This is for major changes, not just replacing a fixture or redecorating. For less comprehensive changes check under the specific category such as plumbing, tile installation or painting.","rolloverShortDesc":"Create a bathroom or substantially alter an old one.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Remodel a Bathroom.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"\u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e Bathroom Remodeling Companies","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":2,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Bathroom Remodel","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Bathroom - Remodel","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Bathroom Remodeling Project","urlName":"Bathroom-Remodel","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Bathroom Remodeling Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"baths, bathroom, shower, bathtub, sink, tub, toilet, tile, general, contractor, renovation","emcCategoryOid":-12001,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":440,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}